--- 
user_16369: 
  salt: aac2ad8d12e2d4857941f9230a8c713e089bc81
  voided: false
  date_created: 2008-01-22 13:42:51 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: jchikuntu
  system_id: 27-3
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-22 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16369
  date_voided: 
  password: b0867a35bd4e94d82c8fef6ed0fb90561aa8dd93
user_16204: 
  salt: ae27ac80369c2433f08c4715b4429125b9e1298
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-12-31 17:04:52 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: data.assistant
  system_id: 23-2
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-02 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16204
  date_voided: 
  password: 558ec4394fb843af749b1e60a99bd83994231e91
user_00004: 
  salt: a4205eff183720fb1222f2b1ea35984b9c6aa12
  voided: true
  date_created: 2005-01-14 00:00:00 +02:00
  creator: 2
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 4
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: Move to production server
  username: burke
  system_id: 4-2
  voided_by: 1
  date_changed: 2006-08-17 15:55:02 +02:00
  user_id: 4
  date_voided: 2006-09-27 19:42:09 +02:00
  password: c15c7ddbbeb61cca54911ff5888ea549fd0bc
user_00005: 
  salt: 1459bff917963b18e75b92358c3ca7f149483747
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-03-14 18:28:40 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 5
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: hamish
  system_id: 5-9
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-09-11 15:40:36 +02:00
  user_id: 5
  date_voided: 
  password: 655d26020a44777ed5a4f8bc7eba5d282e2b06a
user_15897: 
  salt: 21b06b6d4d9757aa6a3ee953d5fef5f4c32c10
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-12-17 16:54:23 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: gchinguwo
  system_id: 22-4
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-12-17 16:58:16 +02:00
  user_id: 15897
  date_voided: 
  password: d49276b0c5c7e4d3045e9315f483569c89266
user_00006: 
  salt: 134f33b6c4c2f7476fc0466cb3798257c4b13e17
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-04-05 16:15:22 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: djazayeri
  system_id: 6-7
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-11 16:35:14 +02:00
  user_id: 6
  date_voided: 
  password: f4445d676f712ab91016dfb8f96d9155edbfc8a
user_16371: 
  salt: d28547eaf7d4f78f1404031d45f616b3e17e6d
  voided: false
  date_created: 2008-02-16 12:06:48 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: bcolumbo
  system_id: 28-1
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-02-16 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16371
  date_voided: 
  password: 8563de5b15296e86d30174451cc4f1ebeee610
user_00007: 
  salt: b0c560ebfc7e57c4ff2d8c45c424a993e6c1f6
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-06-13 12:40:05 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: First pet
  void_reason: ""
  username: ball
  system_id: 7-5
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-08 16:22:29 +02:00
  user_id: 7
  date_voided: 
  password: 275b3ca4de802fdda66d274df90543424707e40
user_15680: 
  salt: a055a45fd9a4c55f714ff8fe1565acac62a47f
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-05-03 20:12:27 +02:00
  creator: 1128
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: asocci
  system_id: 2113-9
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-26 11:59:45 +02:00
  user_id: 15680
  date_voided: 
  password: e4d789c6dbd1e1e40fca85a1283a784c2cb515
user_00008: 
  salt: 67559d893cf2a66c5bb807364d4bf13818928ac
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-06-25 19:16:54 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: jmiranda
  system_id: 8-3
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-11 16:40:24 +02:00
  user_id: 8
  date_voided: 
  password: 654419c2907644bc77ee2787be474fa236a543
user_15877: 
  salt: f4b943c6bd213a94144fb8abbbe65da8c29b885c
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-07-18 15:31:44 +02:00
  creator: 8
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 8
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: cmack
  system_id: 1015-7
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-07-18 15:31:59 +02:00
  user_id: 15877
  date_voided: 
  password: 9c2cc0a9c66749de2ca8482524c43c052c35556
user_16374: 
  salt: 37fd1f3094d3d4511a1d20c725cadb7653129af9
  voided: false
  date_created: 2008-03-10 15:07:30 +02:00
  creator: 15883
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15883
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: fmakombe
  system_id: 29-9
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-03-10 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16374
  date_voided: 
  password: b17f444ce8bfae6653d2ff7af16d958929250e5
user_15878: 
  salt: a1ddb617b95e2a9e2cbefb58ad31ab789b84da
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-10-29 16:08:02 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: ewaters
  system_id: 18-2
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-16 08:37:23 +02:00
  user_id: 15878
  date_voided: 
  password: dd3e13bc413ccbee48c6af6fa4ad18c056c
user_00010: 
  salt: 346095326874963c2143f4dac4d75512267f9de3
  voided: true
  date_created: 2006-07-11 00:08:03 +02:00
  creator: 8
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 8
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: Move to production server
  username: cseebregts
  system_id: 10-9
  voided_by: 1
  date_changed: 2006-07-11 00:08:03 +02:00
  user_id: 10
  date_voided: 2006-09-27 19:42:09 +02:00
  password: ae852158ecd2432ccae248a02a925e92530452
user_00009: 
  salt: 8ae1d04645db2b6bcc8a86e95c2a1bc4f2763
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-06-26 16:13:28 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: schoi
  system_id: 9-1
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-18 16:05:29 +02:00
  user_id: 9
  date_voided: 
  password: 35fcd9961a2c6f30ee93e1538f5538c21cdfe015
user_00021: 
  salt: laWkLAw6QB
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-10-17 15:01:53 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 1
  secret_question: 
  void_reason: 
  username: mikmck
  system_id: ""
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-10-17 15:01:53 +02:00
  user_id: 21
  date_voided: 
  password: 904bf83b60c821aacc43d601b203b124a63fa08f
user_02053: 
  salt: 222e2032538941dc532871d567aaf5ca17daba
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-02-20 10:09:43 +02:00
  creator: 1128
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: What was your favorite activity in high school
  void_reason: ""
  username: mfranke
  system_id: 2053-7
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-18 16:08:31 +02:00
  user_id: 2053
  date_voided: 
  password: 9bb523d7adf2213fb01c525fbd542f8e32e262
user_01128: 
  salt: 8ef0e2833aa46bf6c95875a4fc38bc91b873f95
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-08-17 09:29:42 +02:00
  creator: 6
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: callen
  system_id: 1128-8
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-18 16:06:34 +02:00
  user_id: 1128
  date_voided: 
  password: fe7718ce86ac3315d158f14d5ba1d2167d8a84
user_00011: 
  salt: 337838b0f2808141419df2cd7063de45f5e4bea
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-08-11 11:32:45 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: cgans
  system_id: 11-7
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-26 12:22:24 +02:00
  user_id: 11
  date_voided: 
  password: a2c0ee152e1ddcea71314291119b0e8c53fc060
user_00012: 
  salt: c21a46f8624117658ab064922489fbc9bf75977c
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-08-11 11:34:18 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 12
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: mseaton
  system_id: 12-5
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-29 11:37:47 +02:00
  user_id: 12
  date_voided: 
  password: d8d82bcbb6de68177481fffc3df436b8857b193
user_00001: 
  salt: 9dc1def1a28d34fb4f724222d87fd274cb5b58
  voided: false
  date_created: 2005-01-01 00:00:00 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: admin
  system_id: 1-8
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-12-17 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 1
  date_voided: 
  password: 8aa874cf8f6f783dd3d7f639f2af3a869e09a
user_01954: 
  salt: 8f6a46926be02ff92b5b39e75b70d0ed332e543c
  voided: false
  date_created: 2006-10-04 14:35:59 +02:00
  creator: 6
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: pmanyika
  system_id: 1954-7
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-26 12:16:45 +02:00
  user_id: 1954
  date_voided: 
  password: ea32755718fd80a268cdae68b5aff35d8c753a
user_00002: 
  salt: 322616e6f9756a567b367fb769d847ec8821b81b
  voided: true
  date_created: 2005-01-01 00:00:00 +02:00
  creator: 1
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 2
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: Move to production server
  username: paul
  system_id: 2-6
  voided_by: 1
  date_changed: 2006-08-17 15:59:30 +02:00
  user_id: 2
  date_voided: 2006-09-27 19:42:09 +02:00
  password: 596ebdfa203490199613d618cb8b6be0d0b82d4f
user_16366: 
  salt: 75a2be36d6b272acf7e8981a8a8885b074b7b5
  voided: false
  date_created: 2008-01-20 19:12:08 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: kjoseph
  system_id: 24-0
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-20 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16366
  date_voided: 
  password: 30df5d64da2330cab611aac1fcbddb33fbdae6
user_16367: 
  salt: cd379375e5603173fb444066bd802a992641e2c0
  voided: false
  date_created: 2008-01-20 19:12:49 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: kjobarteh
  system_id: 25-7
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-20 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16367
  date_voided: 
  password: 805bc341b909e6de67fa98037865dba874d4fa
user_15883: 
  salt: 995c2b87799cf0219d60afc6ffbdc36c38ecd469
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-12-17 14:30:04 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: amahaka
  system_id: 20-8
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-21 09:45:02 +02:00
  user_id: 15883
  date_voided: 
  password: 6ff9a9f27850f6f9a15769a550fbebe86373fc
user_15884: 
  salt: 8387bb3fb32674b043c9b1df0a372d0fe246161
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-12-17 14:32:42 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15884
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: qlement
  system_id: 21-6
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-03-12 11:21:41 +02:00
  user_id: 15884
  date_voided: 
  password: 9486f1794a8b9b8a147592f35390715625
user_02112: 
  salt: 8a85a2b5bc8314f39df0bfc68386ef33956d4166
  voided: false
  date_created: 2007-04-30 20:54:54 +02:00
  creator: 1128
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 7
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: jlewey
  system_id: 2112-1
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2007-06-18 16:10:58 +02:00
  user_id: 2112
  date_voided: 
  password: da9ae79cf23e7db9916e036d3a82d9b63741e8
user_16368: 
  salt: 20c44c74ac29a364c33e4ca3e9a47d1254864bc
  voided: false
  date_created: 2008-01-20 19:13:15 +02:00
  creator: 15878
  secret_answer: 
  changed_by: 15878
  secret_question: ""
  void_reason: ""
  username: jcrocker
  system_id: 26-5
  voided_by: 
  date_changed: 2008-01-20 00:00:00 +02:00
  user_id: 16368
  date_voided: 
  password: 33a283cccfad484f6133a3577b94bd7c2ea3b3d
